[
  {"question":"Value set by default in the TARGET attribute is",
    "answer1":"_blank",
    "answer2":"_parent",
    "answer3":"_self",
    "answer4":"_top",
    "correct":"3",
    "score":"20"
  }
,{"question":"To program behavior of web pages, language used is",
  "answer1":"HTML",
  "answer2":"CSS",
  "answer3":"XML",
  "answer4":"JavaScript",
  "correct":"4",
  "score":"20"
}
,{"question":"An element named content have other elements of",
  "answer1":"2 types",
  "answer2":"3 types",
  "answer3":"4 types",
  "answer4":"5 types",
  "correct":"1",
  "score":"20"
}
,{"question":"  Returns a string arguments with trilling blank space removed, is a behavior of",
  "answer1":"starts ( ) function",
  "answer2":"chop ( ) function",
  "answer3":"rtrim ( ) function",
  "answer4":"Both B and C",
  "correct":"4",
  "score":"20"
},
  {"question":"An applet is a program written in Java on the",
    "answer1":"Web",
    "answer2":"Server",
    "answer3":"Domain",
    "answer4":"Client",
    "correct":"2",
    "score":"20"
  }
,{"question":" When an attribute of HTML value contains double quotes, it is necessary to use",
  "answer1":"Single quotes",
  "answer2":"Double quotes",
  "answer3":"Single+Double quotes",
  "answer4":"No quotes",
  "correct":"1",
  "score":"20"
}
,{"question":"To let client know about type of document sent, a CGI program creates",
  "answer1":"Body",
  "answer2":"Header",
  "answer3":"Borders",
  "answer4":"Footer",
  "correct":"2",
  "score":"20"
}
,{"question":"  Hyper Text Transfer Protocol (HTTP) support",
  "answer1":"Proxy Domain",
  "answer2":"Proxy Documents",
  "answer3":"Proxy Server",
  "answer4":"Proxy IP",
  "correct":"3",
  "score":"20"
}
,{"question":"Numeric array values can be sorted through an array method named as",
  "answer1":"sort()",
  "answer2":"length.sort()",
  "answer3":"reverse()",
  "answer4":"compare()",
  "correct":"4",
  "score":"20"
},{"question":"Div element defines section at a",
  "answer1":"Page level",
  "answer2":"Inline level",
  "answer3":"Block level",
  "answer4":"Tab level",
  "correct":"3",
  "score":"20"
}
,{"question":" Internal CSS defines style for",
  "answer1":"Single element",
  "answer2":"Single HTML page",
  "answer3":"Multiple pages",
  "answer4":"Whole Document",
  "correct":"2",
  "score":"20"
}
,{"question":"HTML standard that does not require quotes around attribute values is said to be",
  "answer1":"HTML 1",
  "answer2":"HTML 3",
  "answer3":"HTML 5",
  "answer4":"HTML 7",
  "correct":"3",
  "score":"20"
}
,{"question":" To create Web Pages we use a term, called",
  "answer1":"TCP/IP",
  "answer2":"WWW",
  "answer3":"HTML",
  "answer4":"FTP",
  "correct":"3",
  "score":"20"
}
,{"question":"A browser can retrieve and run an HTML file that has embedded address of",
  "answer1":"Applets",
  "answer2":"Language",
  "answer3":"HTML",
  "answer4":"HTTP",
  "correct":"3",
  "score":"20"
},{"question":"A HTML element known to be <ins>, defines",
  "answer1":"Incapsulation",
  "answer2":"Insertion",
  "answer3":"Instance",
  "answer4":"Instantiation",
  "correct":"2",
  "score":"20"
},
  {"question":" Nontextual information such as digitized photos or graphic images is not a physical part of an",
    "answer1":"WebPage",
    "answer2":"WebData",
    "answer3":"HTML",
    "answer4":"Web-document",
    "correct":"3",
    "score":"20"
  }
,{"question":" A JS method named toString() returns",
  "answer1":"String as a number",
  "answer2":"Alphanumeric pattern as a string",
  "answer3":"Number as a string",
  "answer4":"Exponential as a string",
  "correct":"3",
  "score":"20"
}
,{"question":"A sequence of characters that is treated as a unit is called",
  "answer1":"Arrays",
  "answer2":"Functions",
  "answer3":"Methods",
  "answer4":"Strings",
  "correct":"4",
  "score":"20"
}
,{"question":"When two strings are exactly equivalent Strcmp ( ) returns what?",
  "answer1":"Returns a string",
  "answer2":"Returns 0",
  "answer3":"Returns 1",
  "answer4":"Returns nothing",
  "correct":"2",
  "score":"20"
},{"question":" For finding out one string is equal to another string which function we can use?",
  "answer1":"strpid ( )",
  "answer2":"strpos ( )",
  "answer3":"str ( )",
  "answer4":"All of them",
  "correct":"2",
  "score":"20"
},{"question":" Returns a string arguments with trilling blank space removed, is a behavior of",
  "answer1":"starts ( ) function",
  "answer2":"chop ( ) function",
  "answer3":"rtrim ( ) function",
  "answer4":"Both B and C",
  "correct":"4",
  "score":"20"
}
,{"question":"Which function is used for replacing whole string with an alternate string?",
  "answer1":"Strstr ( )",
  "answer2":"Strrpos ( )",
  "answer3":"Str_replace ( )",
  "answer4":"Replace ( )",
  "correct":"3",
  "score":"20"
}
,{"question":"Stristr ( ) is identical to Strstr ( ) except that",
  "answer1":"The comparison is case independent",
  "answer2":"The comparison start from middle",
  "answer3":"The comparison is case sensitive",
  "answer4":"None of them",
  "correct":"1",
  "score":"20"
}
,
  {"question":" Replacing string from left hand side is known as",
    "answer1":"Slicing",
    "answer2":"Dicing",
    "answer3":"Trailing",
    "answer4":"Leading",
    "correct":"4",
    "score":"20"
  }

]